Ward Brown, I talk with all our customers
and our agents, let's say State Farm.
They trust us with their clients.
I'll go to make sure that we are doing
what they are expecting.
What is a place like State Farm Care most about?
What do they struggle with?
Quality service, obviously price,
and we know all of those.
I just sat with the agency
and they said, what's going on now with your lead time?
And I'll tell 'em that.
We'll tell the customer exactly what we're going to do,
whatever that time is.
Because everything can be different
because of the complexities of the, the job.
We'll know what is going to take for us to do it.
And we tell the client this is what it's going to take
and this is how long it's going to take.
And we nail that so they're happy.
When you see a car and it's ba up
and it's crushed, nobody really knows what happens
to put it back all together.
But what everybody knows
that when it's all put back together
and it's painted so beautifully, everybody can say,
wow, this thing is beautiful.
You know who that was?
It was either everybody put it all back together,
but that final swipe, the magic happens right At that point?
Yes. And that's when our customer come in.
He'll look at his car and he'll be like,
and then when they do that, I can go back to the agencies
and they say, wow, thank you.